Saleh Salehizadeh

Web Developer, Data Analyst

№ +98 (919) 724 6908
⋈ animatorsaleh@gmail.com
in saleh-salehizadeh
if SirSalh
if SirSaleh
if Sirsaleh

Summary

I am Saleh. A full-stack web developer and statistics enthusiast. since childhood, I've been programming for fun, and now I'm developing web for almost 6 years. my main fields of working were entertainment and transportation industries, using Django, PHP, R, MySQL, PostgreSQL and etc. Creating Interesting and useful systems is what connects all my interests and experiences.

Education

2015-2018 M.Sc., Amirkabir University of Technology, Tehran, Mathematical Statistics.

MSc. Thesis

title Simultaneous Tests For High Dimensional Datasets

description Nowadays emergence of new technologies like DNA Mircro-array has been leaded to creating large scale data, which needs new method to analysis. In my Thesis I investigated a model that works on this settings.

2010–2014 B.Sc., Allameh Tababaei University, Tehran, Applied Statistics.

BSc. Project

title Investigation on Mobile-Bank Service Based on SERVQUAL Model

Experience

September Back-end developer, DNBuy Co., Remote Canada.

2020- present *Dnbuy is a international domain and hosting provider website based in Canada.* My task is to participating to new dnbuy service implementation.

Technologies: Django, Nginx, MySQL, jquery, etc.

September Full-stack developer, Abrbar Co., Tehran.

2019- present Abrbar is a project on transportation. My task is to Implementing restful API which currently uses in both drivers and customers android app and Abrbar dashboard, contains all functionalities on ordering, reserving cargo for drivers, financial management and etc.

Technologies: Django, DRF, postgresql, Nginx, reactjs, PWA, jquery, etc.

May 2018- Full-stack django Developer, Boundar Souban Samaneh, Tehran.

April 2020 I was responsible for implementing API endpoints and front-end UI for irasography. I've done full implementation of all features for photographer users and admins. Technologies: django, DRF, postgresql, bootstrap, nginx, etc.

Just a Wordpress Developer, ATNA (Allameh Tabatabei News Agancy), Tehran.

Project website maintenance, including bugs in front-end and implementation of home page slider. used technologies: wordpress, and jquery, MySQL

Sep 2015- Wordpress Developer, Allmaeh Tabatabaei University, Tehran.

Nov 2016 Development of atue.ir website and shop and bank gateway, and implementing new features like woostat plug-in.

Technologies: Wordpress, MySQL, Woocommerce

Languages

English Advanced

Arabic **Beginner**

Japaness **Beginner**

Development and Programming skills

Linux 6 Years User of Linux OS 🔬 ubuntu ubu

Backend django framework ★ ★ ★ ★ ↑ PHP ★ ★ ☆ ☆,

• **Programming**: pure javascript $\bigstar \bigstar \bigstar \bigstar \Leftrightarrow \mathring{\Box}$, jquery $\bigstar \bigstar \bigstar \bigstar \bigstar$, reactjs $\bigstar \overleftrightarrow{\Box} \overleftrightarrow{\Box} \overleftrightarrow{\Box}$

Database ○ MySQL ★★★★★, PostgreSQL ★★★☆

Statistical ○ Programming: R ★ ★ ★ ★ , matlab ★ ★ ☆ ☆

o software: SPSS ★★☆☆, SAS ★★☆☆, Tableaue ★★☆☆☆

Other \circ Languages: python $\bigstar \bigstar \bigstar \bigstar \diamondsuit \circlearrowleft$, $C \bigstar \bigstar \bigstar \diamondsuit \circlearrowleft$, Go $\bigstar \diamondsuit \diamondsuit \diamondsuit \diamondsuit \circlearrowleft$, Bash Scripting Technologies stars/3.png

• Webserver tools: Nginx configuration ★★★☆

• VCS: git ★★★☆, gitflow ★★☆☆

Interests

Interested in learning New topics in technologies and human languages. Reading stackoverflow and other Stackexchange sites and try to answer the questions.

Courses

 AUT and Paris 5 university shared courses on applied statistics (Clustering, Random Forests and Extreme Value Theory)